I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
It will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I'm over
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes in power
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions apart
The golden end is still wrong, but the lowest
The pain that makes us too human after all
Don't want to see before the good show
About the precious one
This car may respond to the call
Don't come up
From under here, no matter what.
Wait, sister.
Hey, Lackus.
Headquarters is checking in.
They want an update.
Now, of all times,
it figures.
It's always when I'm in the middle of eating.
No.
This can't be happening.
So, here we are, Yuichi.
Reliving your most traumatic memory and detail
right down to the blood splatters on the floor.
Huh?
Tomoe, you're alive.
Because of you, she's dead now.
Is that you, brother?
I'm sorry, Mirai.
I didn't mean to wake you up.
You didn't.
I think it's going to be a good day for us.
How are you feeling?
Not too bad.
I think it's going to be a good day for us.
I do, too.
I bet you're hungry.
How about I scrounge up something for you to eat, okay?
Brother, why don't you leave me here to fend for myself so you can move on with your life?
Don't start with this.
Taking care of you is my duty.
But if things don't change, you'll end up dead, too.
No buts, Mirai.
I'm going to make sure we both survive.
You don't mean that.
Not really.
At night, I hear you cry.
About how much you want to leave.
You've grown to hate me.
You wish I'd just die already.
Why?
Why would you say that?
Because despite how noble you try to be, deep down you're a selfish human who only thinks of himself.
Isn't that right, Shihoka Mizuki?
Now I get it.
You're the demon.
Bingo.
But I was right about your thoughts, wasn't I?
I've seen every shameful thing that's floated through your little brain.
I wonder what your sister would say if she knew the truth.
Shut the hell up!
Interesting.
At least one of them appears to be putting up a fight.
It's good to see you.
Even if you did run off and leave us to die with the vampires.
It's not a good idea to imitate people I care about.
Well then.
I thought I'd be able to shake you up by touching on a sore spot.
But you don't appear the least bit rattled.
Now I wonder, why is that?
You're not the first demon who's tried to mess with my head.
So just cut the crap and hand over your power already.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I see what's going on.
You managed to defeat a low-ranking demon like Mi'o'o.
And now you think you've got what it takes to tame a being with actual power.
I could possess your heart and mind without the slightest effort.
You talk big.
But I'm not giving up until I've got a contract with you.
If you've got so much strength, then prove it to me.
Hmm.
You've taken up my blade in search of a demon's might.
The question is why?
I want revenge!
Because you've lost someone important to you?
That's right.
I lost the only family I ever had.
That must have been difficult.
Very well, then.
I can see the desire for revenge burning inside you.
I can offer you unlimited power to achieve it.
Yes.
But it's not quite that simple.
Sorry, you.
To get our strength, you'll have to give yourself over and succumb to your desire for vengeance.
Your unjustly murdered friend is right.
I'd have to possess you to give you the kind of power you want.
No, wait!
You.
You're not going to run off and ditch us again, are you?
You can't just abandon your family.
Brother, you would never do something so dumb.
Now that we're reunited, say you'll live here with us forever!
Yeah, stay with us!
We miss you!
Ah, there it is.
Your weakness.
You have love in your heart, and that's what's holding you back.
We worship desire.
We can't stand love.
Yoichi?
Kimizuki?
Shinoa?
Your new friends.
Forget about them.
You can't become a champion of revenge if you're worried about others.
But my friends.
Don't you think it's unfair that we're dead and you're making a new family?
You left us behind and now you've moved on.
Going to school, training, and making new friends?
You've almost managed to completely forget about us, haven't you?
I have not!
I've never forgotten!
Then forget your new friends and stay with us.
Remember, we're the only family you've ever had.
Shut your mouth.
It's the only way you'll get the strength to avenge us.
Stop it.
You're going to submit yourself to revenge now.
Go to hell!
Stop trying to confuse me, you bastard!
I don't just need your strength to get revenge.
There's more to it.
My aim is bigger.
I want enough power to protect everything and everyone!
Everyone!
This is the trouble with humans.
Your emotions are too complicated.
Love for your friends and fear for their safety compete against your desire for revenge.
I like you.
Your spirit is strong.
I'll agree to follow you as long as it stays that way.
But if I detect weakness in your heart for even a moment, I'll take over your body and soul.
All right.
I guess that's fair.
My name is Ashuramaru.
If you need power, all you have to do is call for me.
Ashuramaru?
Oh, and since you're going to be my master, let me give you some insider information as a gift.
Information?
There's something odd about your composition.
You appear to be human, but about 10% of you is something different.
Could the humans be doing strange experiments on you or something?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't trust your own kind.
Believe me when I tell you mankind is more devious than vampires and demons combined.
Though, it does feel a little weird saying that to a human.
Wait, explain yourself.
What are you suggesting?
Very well.
The contract is now complete.
From this day forward, I shall lend you my strength and abilities.
Open your eyes.
Fan the flames of desire that burn inside of you and forge a blood-stained path in this world.
You eat your own, Yakubia.
You're awake.
How you feeling?
You?
I'm okay.
I beat the demon I wouldn't get too cocky you took your sweet time subjugating the damn thing
you got a cursed deer too of course I did and Joichi
so then who are you you're the one who called me Yoichi if you want to avenge your sister's death
you need a strong set of cursed gear to wield oh that's right I picked up a weapon it was going
to make a contract with I see that's what you are a demon that's right it's pretty mean you chose to
look like this just wait until you see my true form yeah I bet it's pretty nasty so it seems we
have a bit of a problem I've poured over your heart and soul you want to strike back at those
who hurt you but that desire is too weak your soul is gentle and kind you have great love for others
these are all qualities that I despise wait maybe you should look deeper because I do want to avenge
my sister you lie in fact the strongest feeling you have is a relief that you survived the attack
no that's not true not to mention you'd make a terrible fighter you're afraid of conflict and
the thought of your friends and family getting hurt you're weak you don't have the courage to take
a life how are you supposed to get revenge if you aren't capable of killing what I really mean is
you're a coward just a child without a backbone a weakling
but there is one way you can bring hell upon those who murdered your sister give me your body
forever
you don't even have the guts to fight for your life you wouldn't make a suitable master
you're the most pathetic human being I've ever met
oh man this is not good
looks like yoichi didn't have the strength to overcome possession
but I guess having two out of three students pass the black demon tryout isn't that bad at all
huh hey wait where'd he go one two three four little humans all for me
damn it but they've each got curse gears too power hungry humans are such a pain in the ass
my bow
all right now that you two have both got your cursed gear it's time for your first mission
there's a human eating demon loose somewhere in this room
you kimizuki it's up to you guys to deal with it show that bastard who's in control
they'll be my appetizers then the real feast will begin
joichi
well great looks like this demon is coming at us with full force
yoichi must have just been a snack to whet its appetite lieutenant colonel may I share my opinion
please no quiet the situation's getting out of control
hey gurin
how are we supposed to deal with this
joichi is still one of us
look at him your classmate's body assist a vessel now
the only way to save yoichi is to destroy it
what the hell man
there's no way I'm gonna kill one of my friends
don't you get soft on me this is the moon demon company
extermination is your job
or are you guys all talking just here to play around with cursed gear
if you want to get killed that's on you but that monster's not your friend anymore
damn it
if you're serious about using those weapons then show me you've got what it takes to be a soldier
damn it yoichi
sorry sorry but you're going down
what the hell was that
you
let yoichi go you monster
he's one of us
yes
you idiot
don't let up
the demon's not inside the weapon anymore it's in his body
don't do it
we can still save him
interesting
you won't touch me because of the body I'm in
yoichi I know you're in there don't let this stupid demon get the best of you
snap out of it we're supposed to kill vampires together remember
lieutenant colonel these boys are going to get themselves killed
they're not ready for this please don't make them kill yoichi he's their friend
aww you always act like you're so cool but you've got a soft spot for these two problem
students
you've gotten attached haven't you
lieutenant colonel
why don't you step in and kill him then
that'll save the others from being racked with guilt
oh i see
you've got no intention of getting your hands dirty either
let me guess you're just too cute for this as well
joichi get yourself together you're strong enough to beat this thing
it's too late
now die
do it
i won't kill a comrade
but i won't abandon one either
if yoichi's still alive in there then you won't be able to shoot me
you and i are alike in that way
when you've watched your family die in front of you
there's no way that you could ever kill a friend
are you crazy
you'll have to come back or shoot me snap out of it yoichi
die
yoichi
are you gonna stay under that bed and watch your sister be killed or take charge and stop it
this is your last chance to take control
no matter what happens don't come out from under here
i'm sorry
but i can't stay
no more hiding
i'm not gonna run away from my fears anymore
that's why i need the ability to protect those i care about
i want to be able to keep them safe from harm
only then can i make sure nothing like this ever happens again
give me that power you demon
no way
did he just beat it
that's enough
you did a good job
i shot at you
it took way too long to get back
what the hell but why would you kick me for that current
you are you okay
did you know that it would end this way lieutenant colonel
what's that
hell no
i don't really give a damn if one of these kids ends up biting it
you say that but you look like you were really starting to sweat there towards the end of it
you have a rare gift
the guilt you felt for not helping your sister has kept you from living your life
but i think today you overcame that
maybe now you'll be able to reach your full potential
you have a new reason to live
from now on your job is to protect the people who saved your life today
forget revenge
don't get hung up on something so pointless
same goes for you idiot
forget about your previous friends and loved ones
the moon demon company is the only family you'll have now
you're gonna put us first even before your own life
got it
the past means nothing
it's the future that matters
stupid core
okay well you've all got cursed gear and you almost work like a team today
i suppose we should test you out on the front line to see what you're really made of
seriously
that's right
we've got intel that suggests vampires from the kanzai region are planning on reclaiming shinjuku
it's our job to investigate the area
we're finally going to get to hunt vampires
um shouldn't we have some more training first
we don't even get a break after all this
i think these lazy kids are going to be the death of me
we'll be arriving in tokyo shortly
we expect attacks from the japanese imperial demon army
near ikebukuro shinjuku and shibuya
please leave me in caution
did you hear that
well mika
we're going to shinjuku first
we'll be in jeopardy
previous
what do i ride
we'll ride
you
we'll be underwater
we'll be in fruition
don't forget to love our
things
dude
we'll be in episodio
who ap Jorge
should be in
his
wish
he
to
anyways
I need your blood, you read love tonight, I got great light.
I need your blood, you read love tonight, I need your blood, you read love tonight, I got great light.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Mitsuba's Squad.
Next time on Seraph of the End.